xpressbees.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Xpressbees.com

This Privacy Policy explains the policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and transfer of your information by www.xpressbees.com (“Xpressbees/Site/Mobile APP”) for all the services of XpressBees ("Services"). This policy may change as we update, improve and expand the Services, so please check it periodically. By accessing the Site of XpressBees or otherwise using the Services, you consent to collection, storage, and use of the personal information you provide (including any changes thereto as provided by you) for any of the Services offered by us. 

Sources of information

We collect and process the information from you from the following sources to provide better services to all of our users. 

Registration data

This includes basic contact information such as name, gender, age, address, pin code, contact number, occupation, interests and email address etc. provided at the time of registration to use the Site and seeking or obtaining Services from us. 

Paid service data

When you make any payment for the Services, XpressBees or its payment gateway provider may collect your purchase, address or billing information, including your credit card number and expiration date etc. 

Voluntary information

XpressBees may collect additional information at other times, including but not limited to, when you provide feedback, change your Error message need to be informative and display clearly content or email preferences, respond to a survey, or communicate with XpressBees. 

Cookies

XpressBees use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of its Site. Cookies are small files which are stored on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies help us to provide information, which is targeted to your interests. Cookies may be used whether you register with us or not. 

Links to other websites

XpressBees Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from other websites or applications to give you a better service. Such websites or applications are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the application, you are visiting and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. 

Use of your information

The Information as supplied by you enables Error message need to be informative and display us to improve Error message need to be informative and display clearly the Services and provide you the most user-friendly experience. All required information is service dependent and we may use the above said user Information to, maintain, protect, and improve the Services and for developing new services. We may also use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent [with an option to subscribe / unsubscribe (where feasible)]. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major changes, for customer service purposes, billing, etc.). 

Without limitation to the foregoing, your information may be used for the following purposes: 

  * To develop, enhance, market, sell or provide our services, or those of companies with which we have a commercial relationship
  * To provide tips or guidance on how to use our website, inform you of new features on our website, or provide other information that may be of interest to you
  * To evaluate credit standing and to match credit bureau or credit reporting agency information; to investigate, detect and protect ourselves and other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, fraud, theft and other illegal activities
  * To effect a corporate transaction, in connection with the sale, merger, spin-off or other corporate reorganization of our corporation, where the information is provided to the new controlling entity in regular course of business
  * To audit compliance with our policies and contractual obligations

Disclosure of your information

XpressBees shares your information with any third party without obtaining your prior consent in the following limited circumstances: 

  * When it is requested or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these terms or for complying with the applicable laws and regulations
  * XpressBees proposes to share such information within its group companies and employees of such group companies for the purpose of processing personal information on its behalf. We also ensure that these recipients of such information agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures
  * XpressBees may disclose information to third parties to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues or protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or others or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use

Information Security

XpressBees take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. 

Others

We always seek to improve the Services we offer which are dynamic and innovative in nature. We often introduce new features, some of which may result in the collection of new information. If we start collecting substantially new type of information and materially change how we handle your data, we modify this Privacy Policy accordingly.
